http://www.agaysex.com/privacy.html

Submit Story
Bookmark us!
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy for http://www.agaysex.com/
*** 2018 Update. We no longer using cookies for tracking, google doubleclick system or similar. Please check this page for additional info.
We are processing personal data only in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
1. Use of personal data
Personal data is any information relating to an identified or identifiable data
subject, including names, ages, addresses, and email addresses.
A data subject shall be considered identified or identifiable if it is possible
to identify the data subject directly or indirectly in particular on the basis
of one or more factors specific to his/her physical, physiological, economic,
cultural or social identity.
We collect, process and retain personal data to the extent it is necessary to
provide users with our service, especially for the following purposes, e.g.
identifying a registered user, keeping search and video preferences,
keeping the likes of unregistered users, displaying advertisements, keeping
statistics, etc.
We do not collect, process or retain personal data unless allowed under
statutory laws, required by a judicial or governmental order, or the user has
given its consent. We collect all personal data by ourselves and by our means.
Unregistered Users
Persons who visit our website without logging in or registering are unregistered
users. The only personal data we collect from unregistered users is their IP
addresses, which we delete with 30 days after each visit. We do not associate
IP addresses with any of the unregistered users' specific activity (such as
articles/videos they view) on the site.
Unregistered users' IP addresses are only used to prepare aggregate statistics
about the overall activity on our website.
Such aggregate statistics include the countries visitors came from and the types
of electronic device used; they do not contain any personal information.
Registered Users (authors, only if you have created author profile and submitting us stories)
Persons who choose to create an account are registered users. It is possible to
create an account without providing your name. You can maintain your account
under an alias or pseudonym. Upon account creation, new users are sent a
confirmation link by email. If registration is confirmed, you accept to receive
emails to notify specific events such as new friends requests, likes on your
uploads etc.
When users create accounts they are creating profile pages that, if they so
choose, the public and other registered users can view. Registered users can
choose what content to display on their profile, and can individually adjust the
privacy settings on their profile pages to restrict access.
We collect the following data from registered users:
Any information the user submits to us during account creation, such as
username, password, name, email address, password, country, region, and age; and
Any information a user submits to us using our contact form; and
Any content that the user creates (for example, posting a comment or uploading a
photo or video); and
The IP address during the account creation process and whenever a video is
uploaded; and
The clicks and views of the user; and
Any voluntary information the user provides to personalize the user's account
(for example, adding a video to their favourite lists or linking to another
social media account).
This information may contain sensitive information about the user including the
sexual preferences, ethnicity and religion of the user if he/she wishes to share
this information to connect with other users. This information is only retained
as long as the user does not delete or change the information in his/her user
account. The information can only be seen by other registered users and is not
shared or processed in any other way.
Except to the extent detailed above, we do not track registered users' activity
on this website. We only prepares aggregate statistics about clicks and views;
we do not track every click or video watched by users and associate that with
the users' accounts. Please also see additional information about cookies below.
2. Cookies and Google Analytics (Google Analytics not used now at agaysex.com, all served ads are local and not using cookies, cookies used only for authors story submission panel)
We use cookies to collect information about how website is used.
Cookies are text files that are placed by the browser in the memory of a user's
device when website is visited. Website uses session cookies and persistent
cookies:
- Session cookies expire at the end of a browser session. They only enable us to
collect and connect the user’s actions during the particular browser session and
are deleted when the browser is closed or the user logs off.
- Persistent cookies survive a browser session and are stored for a predefined
period of time. We are using persistent cookies with the following information
and for the following purposes:
Identifying a registered user; and
Keeping some search preferences; and
Keeping the likes of the unregistered users; and
Saving the video player's preferences; and
Displaying the advertisements; and
Keeping statistics regarding the speed loading of the pages.
The user can disable the cookie function in his browser options. Please see the
specific information of the browser used for visiting this website. For details
how to control and/or delete cookies, see aboutcookies.org. If cookies are
disabled the user might not be able to use all the functions and services of
website.
In addition, Website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by
Google, Inc. ("Google"), using third-party cookies that enable Google to analyze
the use of website. The information generated by the cookie about the use of
this website is transferred to a Google server in North America. Note that we
have activated Google’s IP anonymization service "anonymize" for Website which
shortens a user's IP address prior to the transfer.
Google will use this information on our behalf to evaluate the use of Website,
to compile reports for activities on Website, and to provide other services to
us relating to Website.
Google Analytics operates under the following terms:
Terms of Service: https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/gb.html
Privacy Statement: https://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/learn/privacy.html
Privacy Policy: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy The user can
prevent Google from collecting and processing the data concerning the use of
Website (including the IP address) by installing a browser-plug-in which is
available under https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
3. Data Security
Note that all data is kept in a secure environment on our main servers located
in Europe. Only restricted access is provided to a limited number of our
employees who are bound to keep all user information confidential.
We protect personal data by using appropriate safeguard procedures and measures
such as:
Access limitation to authorized persons;
Regular backups.
4. User's rights
Any registered or unregistered user, may, at any time, demand information on or
correction and deletion of their personal data that is stored and may object to
any processing of personal data on our contacts page (just send us email with
request).
A user with an account may, at any time, correct or delete his information
directly by using the corresponding interface in his profile.
If a user desires to terminate his account he can do so by contacting us under
our contact page. Upon termination all personal data retained will be
immediately and permanently removed from our servers.
5. Communication
We only contact users by email:
in response to a user's email;
if registration is confirmed in case of a specific event;
if we have serious questions regarding the user's submissions (story or comments); or
if we receive a take-down notice for one or more of the user's uploads.
6. Transfers
We reserve the right to share all information in our possession concerning a
user account and website usage with third parties as necessary to comply with
requirements under applicable law, including the cooperation with public
authorities.
We also reserve the right to store, transfer and process personal data for the
purpose of preventing and prosecuting criminal activities in accordance with
applicable laws.
We do not sell personal information to third parties.
All served ads at this site are LOCAL (images & links) and NOT cookie based. It NOT collect any infomation about you, it just redirect you to advertiser website if you clicked this banner or ad-button. Cookies/personalization are not used for this site ad-functionality.
Hop to:
Select a CategoryBisexual Stories
Coming Out
Erotic Fiction
Erotic Stories
Fantasies
Fetish Stories
First Time Sex
Gay Tips
Random
Harry, time is up.
This is a story about the most strangest things that ever happened in Harry's life. Read to find out...
Read...
Do You Know?
Feel free to submit your own story! Top writers can win prized and be chooses and Top Writer of Year!
Random
Andre, David and the Frenchman
After ten years of life together, my partner and I have found that sharing ourselves with other men keeps our sex life more interesting.
We have never been completly monogomous, but our sex lives are much spicier when we engage in group sex. We are happiest when we have one or two others join us.
Three is okay, but more than four means we lose some control over the event.
Three or four is ideal...
Read...
© 2018 Sex Pleasure Network, gaystory archive and Tube.agaysex.com gay movies.
About | 2257 |
Data Handling & Cookies |
DMCA | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy |
Contacts
Parental controls: Wikipedia.org.
